<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Graph on Akitenkrad's Blog</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/tags/graph/</link><description>Recent content in Graph on Akitenkrad's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/tags/graph/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Modeling Dynamic Heterogeneous Network for Link Prediction using Hierarchical Attention with Temporal RNN</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202208/20220802103319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202208/20220802103319/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Xue, H., Yang, L., Jiang, W., Wei, Y., Hu, Y., &amp;amp; Lin, Y. (2021). Modeling Dynamic Heterogeneous Network for Link Prediction Using Hierarchical Attention with Temporal RNN. Springer, Cham. pp.282–298. https://doi.org/10.1007/978-3-030-67658-2_17 Abstract Network embedding aims to learn low-dimensional representations of nodes while capturing structure information of networks. It has achieved great success on many tasks of network analysis such as link prediction and node classification.</description></item><item><title>Semi-Supervised Classification with Graph Convolutional Networks</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202205/20220520124748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202205/20220520124748/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Kipf, T. N., &amp;amp; Welling, M. (2016).
Semi-Supervised Classification with Graph Convolutional Networks.
Proceedings of the IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition. (2019)
https://doi.org/10.48550/arxiv.1609.02907 Abstract We present a scalable approach for semi-supervised learning on graph-structured data that is based on an efficient variant of convolutional neural networks which operate directly on graphs. We motivate the choice of our convolutional architecture via a localized first-order approximation of spectral graph convolutions.</description></item></channel></rss>