<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2022.07 on Akitenkrad's Blog</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202207/</link><description>Recent content in 2022.07 on Akitenkrad's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202207/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamic Heterogeneous Graph Embedding Using Hierarchical Attentions</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202207/20220727145036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202207/20220727145036/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Yang, L., Xiao, Z., Jiang, W., Wei, Y., Hu, Y., &amp;amp; Wang, H. (2020).
Dynamic heterogeneous graph embedding using hierarchical attentions.
Lecture Notes in Computer Science (Including Subseries Lecture Notes in Artificial Intelligence and Lecture Notes in Bioinformatics), 12036 LNCS.
https://doi.org/10.1007/978-3-030-45442-5_53 Abstract Graph embedding has attracted many research interests. Existing works mainly focus on static homogeneous/heterogeneous networks or dynamic homogeneous networks.</description></item><item><title>Dynamic Network Embedding Survey</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202207/20220726163444/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202207/20220726163444/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Xue, G., Zhong, M., Li, J., Chen, J., Zhai, C., &amp;amp; Kong, R. (2022)
Dynamic network embedding survey
Neurocomputing, 472, 212–223. https://doi.org/10.1016/J.NEUCOM.2021.03.138 Abstract Since many real world networks are evolving over time, such as social networks and user-item networks, there are increasing research efforts on dynamic network embedding in recent years. They learn node representations from a sequence of evolving graphs but not only the latest network, for preserving both structural and temporal information from the dynamic networks.</description></item></channel></rss>