<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Published:2021 on Akitenkrad's Blog</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/tags/published2021/</link><description>Recent content in Published:2021 on Akitenkrad's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/tags/published2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Modeling Dynamic Heterogeneous Network for Link Prediction using Hierarchical Attention with Temporal RNN</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202208/20220802103319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202208/20220802103319/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Xue, H., Yang, L., Jiang, W., Wei, Y., Hu, Y., &amp;amp; Lin, Y. (2021). Modeling Dynamic Heterogeneous Network for Link Prediction Using Hierarchical Attention with Temporal RNN. Springer, Cham. pp.282–298. https://doi.org/10.1007/978-3-030-67658-2_17 Abstract Network embedding aims to learn low-dimensional representations of nodes while capturing structure information of networks. It has achieved great success on many tasks of network analysis such as link prediction and node classification.</description></item><item><title>UnitedQA: A Hybrid Approach for Open Domain Question Answering</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202205/20220514151839/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202205/20220514151839/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Cheng, H., Shen, Y., Liu, X., He, P., Chen, W., &amp;amp; Gao, J. (2021).
UnitedQA: A Hybrid Approach for Open Domain Question Answering.
https://doi.org/10.48550/arxiv.2101.00178 Abstract To date, most of recent work under the retrieval-reader framework for open-domain QA focuses on either extractive or generative reader exclusively. In this paper, we study a hybrid approach for leveraging the strengths of both models.</description></item><item><title>Survey on graph embeddings and their applications to machine learning problems on graphs</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202205/20220509110738/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202205/20220509110738/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Makarov, I., Kiselev, D., Nikitinsky, N., &amp;amp; Subelj, L. (2021).
Survey on graph embeddings and their applications to machine learning problems on graphs.
PeerJ Computer Science, 7, 1–62.
Paper Link Abstract Dealing with relational data always required significant computational resources,domain expertise and task-dependent feature engineering to incorporate structuralinformation into a predictive model. Nowadays, a family of automated graphfeature engineering techniques has been proposed in different streams of literature.</description></item></channel></rss>