<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>At:Round-2 on Akitenkrad's Blog</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/tags/atround-2/</link><description>Recent content in At:Round-2 on Akitenkrad's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/tags/atround-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamic Heterogeneous Graph Embedding Using Hierarchical Attentions</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/posts/papers/202207/20220727145036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/posts/papers/202207/20220727145036/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Yang, L., Xiao, Z., Jiang, W., Wei, Y., Hu, Y., &amp;amp; Wang, H. (2020).
Dynamic heterogeneous graph embedding using hierarchical attentions.
Lecture Notes in Computer Science (Including Subseries Lecture Notes in Artificial Intelligence and Lecture Notes in Bioinformatics), 12036 LNCS.
https://doi.org/10.1007/978-3-030-45442-5_53 Abstract Graph embedding has attracted many research interests. Existing works mainly focus on static homogeneous/heterogeneous networks or dynamic homogeneous networks.</description></item><item><title>Semi-Supervised Classification with Graph Convolutional Networks</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/posts/papers/202205/20220520124748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/posts/papers/202205/20220520124748/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Kipf, T. N., &amp;amp; Welling, M. (2016).
Semi-Supervised Classification with Graph Convolutional Networks.
Proceedings of the IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition. (2019)
https://doi.org/10.48550/arxiv.1609.02907 Abstract We present a scalable approach for semi-supervised learning on graph-structured data that is based on an efficient variant of convolutional neural networks which operate directly on graphs. We motivate the choice of our convolutional architecture via a localized first-order approximation of spectral graph convolutions.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Style Generative Reading Comprehension</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/posts/papers/202205/20220511010217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/blog-akitenkrad/posts/papers/202205/20220511010217/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Nishida, K., Saito, I., Nishida, K., Shinoda, K., Otsuka, A., Asano, H., &amp;amp; Tomita, J. (2020).
Multi-style Generative Reading Comprehension.
ACL 2019 - 57th Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics, Proceedings of the Conference, 2273–2284.
https://doi.org/10.18653/v1/p19-1220 Abstract This study tackles generative reading comprehension (RC), which consists of answering questions based on textual evidence and natural language generation (NLG). We proposea multi-style abstractive summarization model for question answering, called Masque.</description></item></channel></rss>