<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2022.09 on Akitenkrad's Blog</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/</link><description>Recent content in 2022.09 on Akitenkrad's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Learning-based Data Augmentation for network anomaly Detection</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/20220920101324/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/20220920101324/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation al Olaimat, M., Lee, D., Kim, Y., Kim, J., &amp;amp; Kim, J. (2020).
A Learning-based Data Augmentation for Network Anomaly Detection.
International Conference on Computer Communications and Networks, ICCCN, 2020-August.
https://doi.org/10.1109/ICCCN49398.2020.9209598 Abstract While machine learning technologies have been remarkably advanced over the past several years, one of the fundamental requirements for the success of learning-based approaches would be the availability of high-quality data that thoroughly represent individual classes in a problem space.</description></item><item><title>NetWalk: A Flexible Deep Embedding Approach for Anomaly Detection in Dynamic Networks</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/20220915233128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/20220915233128/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Yu, W., Cheng, W., Aggarwal, C. C., Zhang, K., Chen, H., &amp;amp; Wang, W. (2018).
NetWalk: A flexible deep embedding approach for anomaly detection in dynamic networks.
Knowledge Discovery and Data Mining -2018, 2672–2681.
https://doi.org/10.1145/3219819.3220024 Abstract Massive and dynamic networks arise in many practical applications such as social media, security and public health. Given an evolutionary network, it is crucial to detect structural anomalies, such as vertices and edges whose “behaviors” deviate from underlying majority of the network, in a real-time fashion.</description></item><item><title>Spatio-Temporal Graph Convolutional Networks: A Deep Learning Framework for Traffic Forecasting</title><link>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/20220909180827/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akitenkrad.github.io/akitenkrad-blog/posts/papers/202209/20220909180827/</guid><description>Round-1: Overview Round-2: Model Implementation Details Round-3: Experiments Citation Yu, B., Yin, H., &amp;amp; Zhu, Z. (2018).
Spatio-temporal graph convolutional networks: A deep learning framework for traffic forecasting.
IJCAI International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence, 2018-July, 3634–3640.
https://doi.org/10.24963/IJCAI.2018/505 Abstract Timely accurate traffic forecast is crucial for ur-ban traffic control and guidance. Due to the highnonlinearity and complexity of traffic flow, tradi-tional methods cannot satisfy the requirements ofmid-and-long term prediction tasks and often ne-glect spatial and temporal dependencies.</description></item></channel></rss>